Once you get a taste of the good life it's hard to let
go. Even if your life depends on it.
No Man's Land is a action, drama, crime film directed by Peter Werner.
A rookie cop goes undercover to infiltrate a gang of car
thieves led by smooth and charming Ted.
The rookie becomes too involved and starts to enjoy the thrill and lifestyle of
the game, and becomes romanticly involved with the leaders sister.
Ted Varrick, played by Charlie Sheen.
Benjy Taylor, played by D. B. Sweeney.
Ann Varrick, played by Lara Harris.
Lieutenant Vincent Bracey, played by Randy Quaid.
Malcolm, played by Bill Duke.
Frank Martin, played by R. D. Call.
No Man's Land is a 1987 American crime drama film directed by Peter
Werner,  written by Dick Wolf, and starring Charlie Sheen, D.
Sweeney, and Randy Quaid.
The plot follows a rookie cop who goes undercover
and infiltrates a car theft ring.
The film was released on October 23, 1987 and
received mixed reviews from critics.
The tone is emotional.